(Penny:)So, tell me about your day--
how's it going
(Penny:)with the particle detector?
Wow! You remember that?
(Penny:)Yeah, I listen
to what you say.
(Penny:)You're building
a particle detector
(Penny:)using superfluid helium.
(Leonard:)You know, when you
talk like that,
(Leonard:)I want to take you
right here on this table.
(Penny:)And you know
from past experience
(Penny:)this table cannot support
both our weight.
(Penny:)So, how's
the detector going?
(Leonard:)Well, it's tricky working
with superfluids.
(Leonard:)Whatever container
you put them in,
(Leonard:)they kind of
creep up the sides
(Leonard:)and crawl out
all on their own.
(Penny:)Kind of like
Sheldon's ant farm.
(Leonard:)Exactly, except you don't have
a lunatic running around,
yelling, "I fed you sugar water,
why are you biting me?!"
(Leonard:)Come on, this is boring-- you
really want to talk about this?
(Penny:)No, I do.
I-I didn't write
"superfluid helium"
(Penny:)on this napkin for nothing.
(Leonard:)Okay, well...
(Leonard:)This is cool.
(Leonard:)Uh, there's a thing called
"superfluid vacuum theory,"
(Leonard:)where empty space is
imagined as a superfluid
(Leonard:)with all of
its qualities--
(Leonard:)viscosity, density,
surface tension...